Coming up! What's got Joe sleeping on the job?
即将到来！是什么让 Joe 在工作中睡着了？
Why is Sal taking the fall?
为什么 Sal 会跌倒？
And which losing Joker will have major
hunger pains in tonight's punishment?
哪只输掉的小丑会在今晚的惩罚中感到非常饥饿？
Prepare for something amazing!
准备好迎接精彩瞬间吧！
Hey, mustache, what's up?
嘿，小胡子，怎么了？
I want my mommy!
我要我的妈妈！
I will never forgive you!
我永远不会原谅你！
Larry!
拉里！
[Sal] She's all about that 'cado!
[萨尔]她全心全意地专注于那个 'cado！
Today, we're at Focus Pointe Global
今天，我们来到了 Focus Pointe Global
and we're participating in, go
figure, a focus group.
我们正在参加一个焦点小组。
We're also going to be volunteering
to take notes for the group on this computer.
我们还将自愿在这台计算机上为小组做笔记。
The catch is, though, the other
guys will be controlling it.
不过，问题是，其他人将控制它。
Plus, there's a big monitor
in the room
此外，房间里还有一个大显示器
so everyone can see the notes
that are being taken.
这样每个人都可以看到正在记的笔记。
If the notes get too hot to handle
如果音符变得太热而无法处理
and you close that computer
to end your own pain
然后你关闭那台电脑来结束你自己的痛苦
you lose.
你丢失。
You guys can take a seat
wherever you like.
你们可以在任何你想坐的地方坐下。
How's everybody doing?
大家都好吗？
[Q] Moderating is
our boy Chase.
[Q] 主持人是我们的孩子 Chase。
He's going to be guiding the whole
thing exactly where we want it to go.
他将引导整个事情准确地朝着我们希望的方向发展。
Topic today is going to be
artificial intelligence.
今天的主题将是人工智能。
I do need a volunteer
for a notetaker.
我确实需要一个志愿者来做笔记员。
Yeah? Okay, this is the note pad right here.
You can just dictate into it.
是的？好的，这是这里的记事本。你可以口述它。
Good acting. Sold it.
演技好。卖了。
So the first question for today is:
"How would you define AI"?
所以今天的第一个问题是：“您如何定义 AI”？
It's, uh, man made?
这是，呃，人造的？
Uh, computerized?
呃，电脑化了？
I think of robotics, when I think
of artificial intelligence.
当我想到人工智能时，我会想到机器人技术。
Um, I think it's like in many
different, like, platforms now.
嗯，我认为现在很多不同的平台都是这样。
We have it in our cell phones now.
我们现在的手机里有它。
Type, Sal.
类型，Sal.
[Woman] Controllable, but then it
could not be controllable.
[女士]可控，但随后它就无法控制。
[Murr] Look at her!
[Q] She's already in.
[喃喃自语]看看她！[Q] 她已经进来了。
What aspects of AI do you
see in everyday life?
您在日常生活中看到了 AI 的哪些方面？
Okay. Google, Alexa, like Nest.
好。Google、Alexa，就像 Nest 一样。
I think it's like a hub for temperature,
like thermostats?
我觉得它就像一个温度中心，就像恒温器一样？
[Woman] You could like, update
it from your phone...
[女士]你可以喜欢，从你的手机更新它......
and close your garage door.
并关上你的车库门。
-Yeah. Like, um, or even um...
-是的。就像，嗯，甚至嗯......
what is it, like smoke
detectors?
它是什么，就像烟雾探测器一样？
[Q laughing] "It went great."
[Q笑]“进展顺利。”
AI can be destructive in that it's
AI 可能具有破坏性，因为它
removed, like, the humanity
from people you begin to rely on.
就像你开始依赖的人一样，去除了人性。
-Things to do work for us
other than people.
- 为我们工作的事情，而不是人。
What does that mean?
那是什么意思？
Uh, I'm just, what I was gleaning
from the conversation but
呃，我只是，我从谈话中收集到的，但是
Right, but when did we say that?
-No one said that, though.
是的，但我们什么时候这么说的呢？- 不过，没有人这么说。
What steps can be taken, then,
to avoid an AI related disaster?
那么，可以采取哪些措施来避免与 AI 相关的灾难呢？
[Man] So, like, self-driving cars,
I think, I don't know... [unintelligible]
[男子]所以，就像自动驾驶汽车一样，我想，我不知道......[难以理解]
right now it has to have a
driver still in the driver's seat?
现在它必须有一个驾驶员仍然坐在驾驶座上？
[Joe] How do you not close it!?
[乔]你怎么不关它！？
Just like my, my spouse,
is very tech friendly?
就像我一样，我的配偶，对技术非常友好吗？
If I didn't have him, I'd probably
would be, like, still in the Stone Ages.
如果我没有他，我可能还在石器时代。
How do you keep that open!?
你怎么保持开放！？
[Q] Wow! Sal is
unbreakable!
[Q] 哇！萨尔牢不可破！
Our topic today is "vacation".
我们今天的主题是 “假期”。
Q, if you shut the computer,
you lose.
Q，如果关闭计算机，则输了。
So first, let's talk about your
ideal vacation.
那么首先，让我们谈谈您理想的假期。
Whoever, whoever wants
to go first.
无论谁，谁想先走。
Being on the beach and relaxing...
在海滩上放松......
[Man] From one vacation to the next, I always
try to do something that's different.
[男子]从一个假期到另一个假期，我总是尝试做一些不同的事情。
Something that you have
never done before.
您以前从未做过的事情。
[Other man] Like a new place,
new city where you...
[其他男子]就像一个新的地方，新的城市，你......
...and... "free", maybe?
...和。。。也许是“免费”？
[Woman laughing] Yeah,
free is good, yeah!
[女人笑]是的，免费就是好，是的！
[Moderator] On that note, what
are some places that you guys have been to
[主持人]关于这一点，你们去过哪些地方
and, you know, feel free to run down
the list of some places you've been to
而且，你知道的，你可以随意列出你去过的一些地方
and describe them, and...
并描述它们，然后......
[Man] I've been to London. To Rio.
[男子]我去过伦敦。到里约热内卢。
Rio was my favorite.
里约热内卢是我的最爱。
[chuckling] I like Rio.
[轻笑]我喜欢里约热内卢。
Very nice culturally.
在文化上非常好。
Very diverse.
非常多样化。
The one place that I found out
of all the places that I went that
在我去过的所有地方中，我发现的一个地方是
really welcomed a black man.
真的欢迎一个黑人。
They have, like, the second largest
black population other than...
他们拥有除......
North America.
北美洲。
And that's it!
就是这样！
So, today, we are going to
be talking about
所以，今天，我们将讨论
artificial intelligence.
人工智能。
How would you define
artificial intelligence?
您如何定义人工智能？
Type, Murr.
类型，Murr。
It's supposed to help us
have more efficiency.
它应该帮助我们提高效率。
[Brit] ...are computers that can think
or any something that can think.
[英国] ...是可以思考的计算机或任何可以思考的东西。
Something that's programmed
initially.
最初编程的东西。
...the scope to have a conscience, but
...有良心的范围，但是
if we pro... program it with enough...
如果我们支持...用足够的...
it can do all the sums that we can't.
And then...
它可以完成我们不能做的所有总和。然后。。。
[Stripes] I agree with you.
[条纹]我同意你的看法。
The people who manage
that type of technology
管理此类技术的人员
they, like, uh, have the...
他们，就像，呃，有......
It's just so instant, isn't it?
它就是如此瞬间，不是吗？
[Brit] They can be on their phone,
chitty-chatty
[英国]他们可以在手机上闲聊
with their fingers
用他们的手指
but can't have a conversation.
但不能进行对话。
Murr's not closing his laptop. We
have to get him to close his laptop here.
Murr 没有合上他的笔记本电脑。我们得让他把他的笔记本电脑关上。
I think, also, another thing
is like your photos
我认为，还有一件事是你的照片
and if you lose them
如果你失去了它们
[Stripes] In these days
we didn't live the moment and
[条纹]在这些日子里，我们没有活在当下，
we sometimes took a
photo and then
我们有时会拍一张照片，然后
"Ah, yeah, I remember this".
And then like...
“啊，是的，我记得这个。”然后就像......
And then we're able to go
home and go on the computer
然后我们就可以回家使用电脑了
and then, there's a lot of
negative things on there.
然后，那里有很多负面的东西。
A lot of people that
put a lot of negative...
很多人都把很多负面的东西放在了......
[Moderator] Oh, I see
what you're saying.
[主持人]哦，我明白你在说什么了。
And then, it's fueling
people to
然后，它激励人们
think instead of
being connected and
思考而不是连接
[Q, Joe, Sal laughing over dialog]
[Q、Joe、Sal 在对话中大笑]
So... but then I don't
know if I'm drifting off...
所以。。。但随后我不知道我是不是要走神了......
No, I think, I think that you
make some good points.
不，我认为，我认为你提出了一些很好的观点。
Let's review the notes.
让我们回顾一下笔记。
Yeah, she said, uh...
是的，她说，呃......
"Your photos... and if you ... these days...
we want to live in the moment
“你的照片......如果你......目前。。。我们想活在当下
then oh I remember this
like I never had
然后哦，我记得这是我从未有过的
so what do you all think about
that because I think that we're able
那么你们对此有何看法，因为我认为我们能够
I think that we should
have more interaction
我认为我们应该有更多的互动
and be more connected
and we're able to go home
并且联系更加紧密，我们能够回家
and go on the computer
and there are a lot of negative things
然后上电脑，有很多负面的事情
on there... is freaking people...
to be connected...
在那儿......真是该死的人......要连接...
instead of going out in the
world and people can be like
而不是走出去，人们可以像
[stammering] anonymous
[结结巴巴地] 匿名
you know but then I don't
know if I'm drifting off."
你知道的，但我不知道我是不是要走神了。
That's all I got.
这就是我所得到的。
I don't think it was meant
to be verbatim.
我不认为这是逐字逐句的。
Nailed it.
搞定了。
[Q] Wow!
[Q] 哇！
You guys can take a
seat wherever you like.
你们可以在任何你想坐的地方坐下。
How's everyone doing?
大家都好吗？
[Murr] What are you wearing?
[喃喃自语]你穿什么？
Stella's jacket.
斯特拉的夹克。
[Murr] It's Stella's jacket?
[喃喃自语]这是 Stella 的夹克？
[Q] In what reality are you wearing
a jacket that's fifty times too small for you?
[Q] 你穿着一件对你来说小了 50 倍的夹克，在什么情况下？
...be talking about vacations.
...谈论假期。
Sound good?
-Great.
-Cool.
听起来不错？-伟大。-凉。
I need a notetaker.
Anybody want to...?
我需要一个记录器。有人想...？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
You want to n...? Alright, so you're
going to sit here, actually.
你想...？好了，你实际上要坐在这里。
Alright. So first up is, just,
talk about your ideal vacation.
好。所以首先，谈谈你理想的假期。
Ideal vacation, it would be
South Korea
理想的假期，将是韩国
because that's where
I'm from.
因为那是我的家乡。
And I also like San Juan,
Puerto Rico a lot.
我也非常喜欢波多黎各的圣胡安。
That's as far as my...
这就是我的......
[Woman] I want to go
somewhere where it's cold, because...
[女士]我想去一个寒冷的地方，因为......
...go somewhere, like, maybe
like, Connecticut or Vermont.
...去某个地方，比如，也许像康涅狄格州或佛蒙特州。
[Moderator] Uh, how about you?
[主持人]呃，你呢？
[man] For me, it would be somewhere
that allows me to kinda like, go out
[男]对我来说，这将是一个让我有点喜欢出去的地方
like a venture, but it's also
around where
就像一个冒险，但它也在附近
like a water, like a beach...
像水，像海滩......
Anyone can jump in.
任何人都可以加入。
If you could take anyone on vacation...?
如果你能带任何人去度假...？
I'd bring both my parents.
They always loved Aruba.
我会带上我的父母。他们一直很喜欢阿鲁巴岛。
Aruba.
阿鲁巴岛。
[dramatic sting]
[戏剧性的刺痛]
If you could take anyone on vacation...?
如果你能带任何人去度假...？
I'd bring both my parents.
They always loved Aruba.
我会带上我的父母。他们一直很喜欢阿鲁巴岛。
Aruba.
阿鲁巴岛。
So we're going to move on
to, uh, to, like, hotels.
所以我们要继续讨论酒店。
Would you prefer to stay
in a hotel, or you just like...
您是想住在酒店，还是只想住在酒店里......
or use home sharing websites?
或者使用家庭共享网站？
[woman] Airbnb's more,
like, affordable...
[女人]Airbnb 更实惠......
Let's say for example you're
going to, like, uh,
例如，假设您要，例如，呃，
you know, like, a city,
like L.A.?
你知道，比如，像洛杉矶这样的城市吗？
If you go to someone's home,
whatever area they're around...
如果你去某人的家，无论他们周围是什么地方......
[man] Yeah, I like, um,
Airbnb is, like, the way to go.
[男]是的，我喜欢，嗯，Airbnb 就是要走的路。
Like, when I think of,
like, hotels
就像，当我想到酒店时
I thinking about like, me going
to a conference
我想着，我去参加一个会议
or something like that. And
I'm just like...
或类似的东西。我就想......
[Q, Murr, Sal] Ohhhh! Ohhhh!
[Q， 穆尔， 萨尔]哦！哦！
We're never going to get this guy.
We're never going to get this guy!
我们永远都抓不到这个家伙。我们永远也抓不到这个家伙！
[Moderator] What about you guys?
-Ummm...
[主持人]你们呢？-嗯......
I think I'd prefer to be like,
active and/or, like, relaxing.
我想我更喜欢像、活跃和/或放松。
I think personally it's because like...
[Murr] Uh oh!
我个人认为这是因为......[喃喃自语]呃哦！
[Murr] His blood sugar is low.
[喃喃自语]他的血糖很低。
[man] I work as like a consultant,
like an analyst...
[男]我像顾问一样工作，像分析师......
so I do like numbers
a lot, everyday
所以我每天都非常喜欢数字
[laughing over dialog]
[对话中大笑]
Q had to "force quit" this one, so
he's first up on the loser board.
Q 必须 “强制退出” 这个，所以他首先出现在失败者董事会上。
Today, we're at Morton
Williams Supermarket
今天，我们在 Morton Williams 超市
trying to get a witness
to help us out with a little
试图找一个证人来帮助我们
insurance fraud.
保险欺诈。
After calling attention to
an "unsafe" store condition,
在提请注意“不安全”的商店状况后，
we'll tell a fellow shopper we
wouldn't mind having an "accident"
我们会告诉其他购物者，我们不介意发生 “事故”
in order to collect money.
为了收钱。
Then the other guys will give us
a weird reason we need the money
然后其他人会给我们一个奇怪的理由，我们需要这笔钱
and we're going to take
a huge dive.
我们将进行一次巨大的潜水。
When the store "manager" comes
out to see what happened,
当店“经理”出来查看发生了什么事时，
we'll have to get the fellow
shopper to back up our story.
我们得让其他购物者来支持我们的故事。
If they don't back up your
story, you lose.
如果他们不支持您的故事，您就输了。
[All] Whoa whoa whoa!
[全部]哇哇哇哇！
[Joe] Okay, so basically, we're
doing our best pratfall work today.
[乔]好的，基本上，我们今天正在做我们最好的 pratfall 工作。
We're going to take out an
endcap and ask somebody to, uh,
我们要拿出一个端盖，然后请人，呃，
corroborate our story.
证实我们的故事。
[Joe] The manager today is being
played by one of our favorites:
[乔]今天的经理由我们最喜欢的一位扮演：
our comedy producer John.
我们的喜剧制作人约翰。
Who actually, in reality, did
manage a grocery store.
实际上，谁确实管理着一家杂货店。
Keeping it real.
We keep it real.
保持真实。我们保持真实。
[Q] Here we go.
[Q] 我们开始吧。
Do you think that someone could
trip on this thing on the end?
你认为有人会在最后被这个东西绊倒吗？
It's a little bit on the...
I'm a little nervous for people.
它有点......我对人们有点紧张。
I think it might be...
-On this corner?
我想可能是......-在这个角落？
Yeah, right here. I think it's like
I'm afraid someone's knock in
是的，就在这里。我觉得这就像我害怕有人敲门一样
to it and it's going to fall
one someone. Right?
-Oh my god.
到它，它会落在一个人身上。右？-哦，我的上帝。
Yeah, I think you're right.
是的，我认为你是对的。
Yeah, someone could fall and
really, and really hurt themselves.
是的，有人可能会跌倒，然后真的、真的伤到自己。
They'll probably sue the grocery store.
-That's true.
他们可能会起诉杂货店。- 这是真的。
Believe me, I could use
the money myself.
相信我，我可以自己用这笔钱。
"My mother needs a
breast reduction."
“我妈妈需要缩胸。”
My mom needs a
breast reduction.
我妈妈需要乳房缩小术。
Yeah...
是的。。。
I know, right?
我知道，对吧？
They were on the end, here.
他们在终点，在这里。
I can't believe you did this!
我简直不敢相信你做了这个！
[Joe] Send in the manager.
[乔]请送管理器。
What happened?
-I'm sorry.
发生了什么事？-对不起。
Are you the manager?
-Yeah.
您是经理吗？-是的。
[Q] Look at the face!
[Q] 看那张脸！
These, uh, these were
stacked on the end here.
这些，呃，这些都堆在了这儿的最后。
Not a good place.
不是一个好地方。
I was walking. I tripped,
and they all fell.
我走路。我绊倒了，他们都倒下了。
She saw it. She saw it!
她看到了。她看到了！
Ma'am, is that true? Because I
have to fill out an accident report.
马，这是真的吗？因为我必须填写事故报告。
Yeah, yeah, you know
because she agreed with me.
是的，是的，你知道的，因为她同意我的看法。
Okay. Alright.
-[Joe] You lost!
好。好。-[Joe] 你输了！
Alright.
好。
This look high to you?
这个看起来高吗？
Like a safety issue?
喜欢安全问题？
I just worry that it would, like,
fall on a child or something like that.
我只是担心它会落在孩子身上或类似的东西。
That's a big lawsuit.
这是一场大诉讼。
That's big money.
那可是一大笔钱。
I mean, honestly, I
could use the money.
我的意思是，老实说，我可以用这笔钱。
"I don't know if you can tell by looking at me..."
-I don't know if you can tell by looking at me...
“我不知道你看我能不能看出来......”——我不知道你看我能不能看出来......
"But I want to open a vape shop."
-But I want to open a vape shop.
“但我想开一家电子烟店。”- 但我想开一家电子烟店。
[Murr] Oh, oh oh oh!
[喃喃自语]哦，哦！
[Joe] Oh, banana peel. Nice!
-[Murr] No!
[乔]哦，香蕉皮。好！-[Murr] 不！
Ohhhh.
哦。
Ohhhh!
哦！
Ohh.
哦。
Oh, I'm hurt.
哦，我受伤了。
Ohhhh.
哦。
Sir, you alright?
先生，您还好吗？
Sir, there was a banana. I slipped.
I fell into this thing.
先生，有一根香蕉。我滑倒了。我陷入了这个困境。
Oh, oh, my neck!
哦，哦，我的脖子！
She saw. She's my witness.
她看到了。她是我的证人。
Call an ambulance.
-What happened?
叫救护车。-发生了什么事？
I got to fill out an accident report.
Did you witness this?
我得填写一份事故报告。你目睹了吗？
He did not?
他没有？
What happened?
发生了什么事？
Ohh. Call an ambulance!
哦。叫救护车！
This is something. Did you
see this display?
这是很了不起的。您看到这个显示了吗？
This is a disaster waiting
to happen, don't you think?
这是一场等待发生的灾难，你不觉得吗？
Possibly.
可能。
I mean, someone could trip over...
the edges are not straight.
我的意思是，有人可能会绊倒......边缘不直。
I got to tell you, I could
actually use the money myself.
我得告诉你，我自己其实可以用这笔钱。
Here's why.
-[Joe] "I love to gamble."
原因如下。-[Joe] “我喜欢赌博。”
I love to gamble.
我喜欢赌博。
And I just got back
from "Korean Vegas".
我刚从“韩国维加斯”回来。
I...
我。。。
I just got back
from "Korean Vegas".
我刚从“韩国维加斯”回来。
You can't beat the bank,
you know what I'm saying?
你不能打败银行，你知道我在说什么吗？
You know what?
你知道吗？
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa!
哇
Ahhhh!
啊！
Who put this display...
No, I'm not okay!
谁把这个显示器...不，我不行！
Where's the manager?
Who put the display like this?
经理在哪里？谁把显示器放成这样？
[Joe] He's out, he's gone!
[乔]他出去了，他走了！
Matt <3 Ali
马特 <3 阿里
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa!
哇
Ahhhh!
啊！
Where's the manager?
Who put the display like this?
经理在哪里？谁把显示器放成这样？
[Q] Look at him, he's out of there.
[Joe] He's out, he's gone!
[Q] 看看他，他已经离开了。[乔]他出去了，他走了！
Send in the manager!
送来经理！
The guy up there in the
register saw what happened.
收银台上的那个人看到了发生的事情。
In the hat on.
-In the hat witnessed it?
在帽子上。-在帽子里目睹了它？
Stay right here, we'll fill out...
-Bring him over here, he'll tell you what happened.
待在这里，我们会填写......- 把他带到这里，他会告诉你发生了什么。
It was crazy.
这太疯狂了。
The manager had to go chase this guy down.
经理不得不去追赶这个家伙。
You think he's going to vouch for you?
你觉得他会为你担保吗？
The manager?
经理？
John!
John！
He's so real. I'm buying into it.
-You're buying into it.
他太真实了。我正在接受它。- 你买进了它。
Here we go. Here we go.
来吧。来吧。
Sir?
-Yes.
先生？-是的。
He saw what happened, that
this whole display was...
他看到了发生的事情，这整个展示是......
What?
什么？
No honor among thieves,
apparently?
显然，在盗贼中没有荣誉吗？
Alright, this is Joe's...
his body was literally built for this.
好吧，这是乔的......他的身体真的就是为此而生的。
Uh huh. Made for
falling into cereal.
嗯。适合掉入麦片。
[dog barking in the distance]
[远处的狗吠声]
Does that dog need a home?
-[Q] No, no!
那只狗需要一个家吗？-[Q] 不，不！
Don't adopt that dog, Joe.
不要收养那只狗，乔。
[Murr] Doesn't... dog need a home.
[喃喃自语]不。。。狗需要一个家。
Alright, here you go.
好了，给你。
They got good 'cados [avocados] today.
他们今天吃到了很好的 'cados [鳄梨]。
Yeah, the 'cados are nice.
是的，'cados 很好。
Did you see this here?
你在这里看到了吗？
This is in a bad spot here.
This seems dangerous, right?
这在这里处于一个糟糕的位置。这看起来很危险，对吧？
It's a lawsuit waiting to happen.
这是一场等待发生的诉讼。
They better be careful. They might
find themselves in a lawsuit, right?
他们最好小心点。他们可能会发现自己陷入诉讼，对吧？
I could use some money, actually.
实际上，我可以用一些钱。
"My son needs some
bull#### operation."
“我儿子需要一些公牛#### 手术。”
Just found out my son needs
some bull#### operation.
刚刚发现我儿子需要一些公牛#### 手术。
You know what? That's going
to be a way to help him out.
你知道吗？这将是帮助他的一种方式。
[Q] Here we go.
[Q] 我们开始吧。
Hyup!
哎呀！
Ohhh, god!
天啊！
Ohhhh! Ohhhhh.
-Oh my god, look at the crowd.
哦！哦。-哦，天哪，看看人群。
[Q] She's not even stopping the
squeezing of the 'cados.
[Q] 她甚至没有停止对 'cados 的挤压。
She's all about that 'cado!
她全心全意地专注于那个 'cado！
You alright?
-Yeah, this is in a bad spot.
你还好吗？- 是的，这很糟糕。
Alright, alright. -Yeah, I mean she saw
the whole thing, this lady over here
好吧，好吧。-是的，我是说她看到了整件事，这边的这位女士
Who saw everything?
谁看到了一切？
The lady with the 'cados.
-Okay.
那个戴着 'cados.-好。
I got to fill out an accident
report. You wit...?
我得填写一份事故报告。你聪明...？
You didn't see...?
你没看到...？
[Joe] You saw the whole thing.
[乔]你看到了整个事情。
I was getting my avocados!
我得到了我的鳄梨！
Yeah, I know. You'll back me
up? The whole thing?
是的，我明白。你会支持我吗？整件事？
I was choosing my avocados.
我正在选择我的鳄梨。
I know, but you'll back me
up. My son...?
我知道，但你会支持我。我儿子。。。？
You'll back me up?
你会支持我吗？
No, I'm not getting
you to say something...
不，我不是要你说什么......
So, nobody backed us up?
所以，没有人支持我们？
Sorry, John.
对不起，约翰。
I'm sorry too.
我也很抱歉。
All the guys claims were denied
所有家伙的说法都被拒绝了
so Q is tonight's big loser.
所以 Q 是今晚的大输家。
So Q is our loser, and today
he is "volunteering"
所以 Q 是我们的失败者，今天他是 “志愿服务 ”
at the Long Island Cares Food Bank.
在 Long Island Cares Food Bank。
And he's hungry.
而且他饿了。
You're going to need this, buddy.
你会需要这个的，伙计。
What, did it take you 2 seconds
to come up with this one?
什么，你花了 2 秒钟才想出这个？
One for them, one for you.
一个给他们，一个给你。
-There you go!
-Get in there!
-给你！-进去！
[Joe] Here's the volunteer
extraordinaire, Brian "Q" Quinn
[乔]这是杰出的志愿者 Brian “Q” Quinn
coming to do some good.
来做一些好事。
Just over here, doing my
civic duty.
就在这边，履行我的公民义务。
Alright, so now Q's hungry. And that's
basically the punishment.
好了，现在 Q 饿了。这基本上就是惩罚。
[Murr] Help yourself. Important
to note:
[喃喃自语]帮助自己。重要注意事项：
for every one thing Q ruins,
因为 Q 每毁掉一件事，
we're replacing it with 3
brand new items.
我们将用 3 件全新的商品替换它。
So, we're actually
doing some good.
所以，我们实际上正在做一些好事。
Woof.
汪。
Work up a hunger, looking
at all this food, you know?
饿着肚子，看着所有这些食物，你知道吗？
[Murr] Here we go.
[喃喃自语]来吧。
I should've ate breakfast.
我应该吃早餐的。
[Murr] Oh, Q.
[喃喃自语]哦，问。
Don't eat the food for the needy.
不要吃穷人的食物。
[Murr chuckling] No, bud.
[喃喃自语]不，伙计。
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
[jar lip pops]
[罐子嘴唇爆裂]
[Murr] Oh ho ho!
[喃喃自语]哦呵呵！
[Sal] It is on!
[萨尔]它开始了！
[Murr] Oh, Q.
[喃喃自语]哦，问。
Don't eat the food for the needy.
不要吃穷人的食物。
[Murr chuckling] No, bud.
[喃喃自语]不，伙计。
[jar lip pops]
[罐子嘴唇爆裂]
[Murr] Ohhhh. She gave you a look.
[喃喃自语]哦。她看了你一眼。
It is on!
它开始了！
Oh my god. How weird do you feel?
哦，我的上帝。你感觉有多奇怪？
The... the hate is... instant.
这。。。仇恨是......瞬间。
I know. I know.
We can feel it.
我知道。我知道。我们能感觉到。
[Joe] You want to
open something else?
[乔]您想打开其他内容吗？
[lid tearing open]
[盖子撕开]
Bud, we, bud, we put a fork
in your pocket.
巴德，我们，巴德，我们把叉子放在你的口袋里。
[Joe] There's a fork
in your cargo pants.
[乔]你的工装裤里有个叉子。
Ohh, god.
天啊。
[Murr] Oh, she's going to talk. She's
going to talk! [Joe] She's going to report you.
[喃喃自语]哦，她要说话了。她要说话了！[乔]她要举报你。
She's steaming. She's
steaming. Rightfully so.
她热气腾腾。她热气腾腾。这是理所当然的。
[Murr] Alright, Q.
[喃喃自语]好的，Q.
[Cole] Sir?
[科尔]先生？
We can't eat the donations.
我们不能吃这些捐款。
That's Cole, one of our
producers.
我是 Cole，我们的制片人之一。
He's our inside man.
他是我们的内线。
We can't be eating the food.
我们不能吃这些食物。
Got it. Uh, it was dinged.
明白了。呃，它被叮叮当当。
I don't see a ding, sir.
我没有看到叮当声，先生。
Keep cooking, guys. Everyone's
doing well. -Loud and clear, loud and clear.
继续做饭，伙计们。每个人都过得很好。- 响亮而清晰，响亮而清晰。
Alright, new guys. Fire it up.
-New guys!
好了，新人。点燃它。-新人！
[Sal] Snack time!
[萨尔]点心时间！
[crunching]
[嘎吱嘎吱]
[Sal] Oh, my god.
[萨尔]哦，我的上帝。
Disapproving looks being
shot everywhere.
到处都是不赞成的眼神。
You're like a human raccoon.
你就像一只人类浣熊。
He is "scurraging" for food.
他正在 “四处寻找” 食物。
[Q] They hate me.
[Q] 他们恨我。
I feel their hate for me
coming off in waves.
我感觉到他们对我的仇恨一波又一波地消失。
[Murr] Getting hungry, bud?
[喃喃自语]饿了，伙计？
Just whisper, "what else
this place got?"
只是低声说，“这个地方还有什么？
What else this place got?
这个地方还有什么？
[Murr] Look at this.
[喃喃自语]看看这个。
[Murr and Sal] Q, oh my god!
[穆尔和萨尔]Q，天哪！
[Joe] He's full-blown opening
a can on the table.
[乔]他正在全力以赴地打开桌子上的一个罐头。
[Sal] Oh, what is that? What is that? Corn?
[Murr] It's, uh, corn.
[萨尔]哦，那是什么？什么？玉米？[喃喃自语]这是，呃，玉米。
[Sal] Ugh, jellied corn, milk, ham?
[萨尔]呃，果冻玉米、牛奶、火腿？
Dude, your ass is going to be
making a donation in a few minutes.
伙计，你的屁股几分钟后就要捐款了。
[Joe, Murr, Sal] Ohhhh!
[乔、穆尔、萨尔]哦！
Oh, but it was dinged?
哦，但它被叮叮当当了？
It wasn't? It was dinged.
不是吗？它被叮叮当当。
All dinged. All dinged.
全都叮叮当当。全都叮叮当当。
All dinged!
全都叮叮当当！
This is what we knew
would happen,
这就是我们知道会发生的事情，
That good people would rise up.
-Yes.
好人会起来。-是的。
And take a stand against
this piece of garbage. -Yep.
并反对这块垃圾。-是的。
Okay.
好。
[Cole] Alright, let's uh...
I'm going to go talk to him.
[科尔]好吧，呃......我要去和他谈谈。
Sir, are you eating more food?
先生，您吃的食物多了吗？
No. No. No.
不。不。不。
No no no no. No!
不，不，不，不。不！
What is this, then, sir?
那么，先生，这是什么呢？
The... the...
这。。。这。。。
Sir, you can't open the food.
-Got it.
先生，你不能打开食物。-明白了。
Last time. Two strikes.
Two strikes.
上次。两次打击。两次打击。
This was open before, though.
不过，这以前是开放的。
We should stop eating and we
should pack it
我们应该停止进食，我们应该打包
and then we can all get
out of here. -Got it.
然后我们都可以离开这里。-明白了。
[Murr] Oh, this is tense.
[Sal] I can't
[喃喃自语]哦，这很紧张。[萨尔]我不能
take it anymore!
再来吧！
Brian, hi.
Brian，您好。
Don. Nice to meet you, Don.
Thank you.
Don. 很高兴认识你，Don. 谢谢你。
Oh, man.
哦，伙计。
Don is the best!
Don 是最好的！
[Murr] Q, these people need
to see you eat some ham.
[喃喃自语]Q，这些人需要看到你吃点火腿。
Can you trying opening a
ham with the can opener?
您可以尝试用开罐器打开火腿吗？
[metal cutting]
[金属切削]
[Sal] He's pointing him out!
[萨尔]他在指着他！
[Joe] Don's going to get Cole.
[乔]Don 会得到 Cole。
[Cole] Brian!
-Hey, what's going on, man?
[科尔]布莱恩！-嘿，这是怎么回事，伙计？
I just saw you eating more food.
我刚刚看到你吃得更多了。
I'm not eating anything!
我什么都没吃！
Well, he just told me that you...
嗯，他刚才跟我说你......
[muffled over a mouth full of food]
He told you!?
[含糊不清的嘴]他告诉你的！？
Don!
唐！
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, I hear what
you're saying, but...
是的，我听到你在说什么，但是......
Yeah.
是的。
Hmmmm.
嗯。
[Joe] Don is an angel.
[Sal We love Don.
[乔]唐是个天使。[Sal 我们爱 Don。
[together] We love Don! We love Don!
[一起]我们爱 Don！我们爱 Don！
Is this another can of
cooked ham?
这是另一罐煮熟的火腿吗？
That... [stammers]
那。。。[结结巴巴]
This is your second
cooked ham can?
这是你的第二个煮熟的火腿罐头？
[Sal] Oh, we got Cole laughing!
[萨尔]哦，我们让 Cole 笑了！
[Joe] Get him out.
[Murr] There you go.
[乔]把他赶出去。[喃喃自语]给你。
[Murr] "I'm going to volunteer
to leave."
[喃喃自语]“我要自愿离开。”
No, I volunteer to leave.
I volunteer to leave.
不，我自愿离开。我自愿离开。
You didn't fire
me, I quit.
你没有解雇我，我辞职了。
Q, if you're hungry, you
can take some stuff to go.
问：如果你饿了，你可以带一些东西带走。
[Murr] Yeah, your backpack is up
there. Get your bag to leave.
[喃喃自语]是的，你的背包就在那里。拿你的包离开。
And pack some stuff
up to go.
并收拾一些东西准备出发。
[Joe] Do a quick
round to go.
[乔]快速转一圈即可。
No no no no no!
不！
This guy's going to literally
put you in a full nelson.
这家伙真的会让你陷入困境。
Well, it's not a Board
of Health thing.
嗯，这不是卫生委员会的事情。
No, I'm gone.
不，我走了。
[Murr] Oh! Run run run!
[喃喃自语]哦！Run Run Run！
[Joe] Out the door in shame.
[乔]羞愧地走出了门。
There's the second can
of cooked ham!
还有第二罐煮熟的火腿！
Brian! You didn't even
eat the first one!
布莱恩！你甚至没有吃第一个！
That was horrible.
那太可怕了。
Look at how much I'm sweating.
Dude, it was so bad.
看看我出汗多少。伙计，这太糟糕了。
Wow.
-It was so nerve-racking.
哇。-这太伤脑筋了。
Wow. So Q "ate it" in
tonight's punishment
哇。所以 Q 在今晚的惩罚中“吃了”
but we're going to
"donate" some bonus footage
但我们将“捐赠”一些额外的素材
and a behind-the-scenes
look at how it happened.
以及幕后花絮，看看它是如何发生的。
Eat up!
吃光！
I got a ham in my teeth.
I got to go brush.
我的牙齿里有一根火腿。我得去刷牙。
Yeah. Go, go.
是的。走吧，走吧。
That was terrible!
太可怕了！
Murr, this is a, this is
a weird one today, huh?
喃喃，这是，今天很奇怪，是吧？
How do you mean?
-This punishment is unlike...
你是什么意思？- 这种惩罚不像......
You, you are tall!
你，你个子高啊！
This is me without shoes.
You've got shoes on, admittedly.
这就是没有鞋子的我。诚然，你已经穿上了鞋子。
But watch me, watch
me without shoes.
但是看着我，看着我没穿鞋。
Oh.
哦。
See?
-Yeah. He's got lifts.
看？-是的。他有电梯。
This is tough for you
because I know that you
这对你来说很艰难，因为我知道你
you know, you donated
your time
你知道，你贡献了你的时间
as a firefighter.
作为一名消防员。
I mean, I guess
you got paid for it.
我的意思是，我猜你已经为此付出了代价。
Yeah.
-But you're a hero
是的。- 但你是个英雄
and then today you have
to kind of be a "zero".
然后今天你必须成为 “零”。
Yeah, but I'm more used to
being a "zero" than a hero.
是的，但我更习惯于成为“零”而不是英雄。
That's not true.
那不是真的。
Uh, I just like to help, man.
呃，我就是想帮忙，伙计。
Yeah. What did you rat me
out on the corn for?
是的。你把我赶出去干什么？
Well, I wouldn't have to lie
if you didn't point it out.
好吧，如果你不指出来，我就不必撒谎。
Do you know the
challenge where Joe
你知道乔的挑战在哪里
is... we're working in
Organic Avenue?
是。。。我们在 Organic Avenue 工作？
Yeah.
-And, the juice place?
是的。- 还有果汁店？
And Joe keeps
drinking the milk
乔继续喝牛奶
out of the fridge?
-Yeah.
从冰箱里出来了？-是的。
That's essentially
what this is, worse.
这基本上就是更糟糕的。
People have donated their
time; they've donated food.
人们贡献了他们的时间;他们捐赠了食物。
And Q is wasting their
time and eating their food.
而 Q 正在浪费他们的时间并吃他们的食物。
Beautiful.
美丽。
Oh, I know the show.
哦，我知道这个节目。
It says "cooked ham",
does that mean
上面写着 “cooked ham”，这是什么意思
You can't, you can't eat it
room temperature?
你不能，你不能在室温下吃吗？
Let's find out.
让我们来了解一下。
Let's find out, then.
那么，让我们来了解一下。
Any bread in here?
这里有面包吗？
Everything about that
was horrible.
一切都很可怕。
Everybody hated me
within 2 seconds. -I know.
每个人都在 2 秒钟内讨厌我。-我知道。
I'm not used to, like, that.
我不习惯，就像这样。
It's so different. They're
the nicest people
这太不同了。他们是最好的人
for donating their time.
贡献他们的时间。
And, and you're
the worst person.
而且，你是最糟糕的人。
Peanut butter, yeah!
花生酱，是的！
[Sal] That's one you
won't see him eat.
[萨尔]那是你不会看到他吃的。
Q's deathly allergic to it.
Q 对它过敏得要命。
No, that's not true.
-He just doesn't like it.
不，那不是真的。- 他就是不喜欢。
"He'll die"? "He'll die"?!
“他会死”？“他会死的”？！
[stammers] like, his throat, right?
[结结巴巴地] 比如，他的喉咙，对吧？
Peanut butter gives me
a big headache
花生酱让我头疼不已
So, I can guarantee none of these
are dinged. You know what I mean?
所以，我可以保证这些都没有被打砸。你知道我的意思？
[Joe] Look at this guy!
[乔]看看这家伙！
Wow. And Cole! Cole
was reaming into you.
哇。还有科尔！科尔正在向你敞口。
What was up with Cole, man?
科尔怎么了，伙计？
Why would Cole come
at me like that?
为什么科尔会这样冲我呢？
Uh, are you eating
more food?
呃，你吃的食物多了吗？
No.
-And don't tell me it was dinged.
不。- 别告诉我它有叮当声。
This is donations that
we need for churches
这是我们教会需要的捐款
and for people in need.
-No, I get it.
以及为有需要的人服务。- 不，我明白了。
I didn't open anything new.
我没有打开任何新的东西。
Q is kind of like your boss.
Did it feel good to
Q 有点像你的老板。感觉好吗
Very much like my boss.
很像我的老板。
Right. Did it feel good? Were
you, like, letting loose on him?
右。感觉好吗？你是不是，对他放纵了？
Yeah, yeah. It was finally
I was protected.
是的。我终于得到了保护。
I was allowed to.
我被允许这样做。
[Sal] Well, let's keep cutting
back to the clip where you laugh.
[萨尔]好吧，让我们继续切回你笑的片段。
This is your second
cooked ham can?
这是你的第二个煮熟的火腿罐头？
We got Cole laughing!
我们让 Cole 笑了起来！
[talking over each other]
[互相交谈]
####! ####! Ohhh.
Son of a...
####!####!哦。一个的儿子...
I hate him!
我恨他！
[Sal] White, brand new sneakers.
[萨尔]白色全新运动鞋。
It's dripping!
它在滴水！
White, brand new. White
and brand new sneakers.
白色，全新。白色和全新的运动鞋。
It's dripping out of his shoe!
它从他的鞋子里滴下来了！
I mean, this is next
level, guys.
我的意思是，这是下一个级别，伙计们。
What are we going
to do about this?
我们该怎么办？
Murray just dropped a
full iced tea on Sal.
Murray 刚刚给 Sal 倒了一整杯冰茶。
I mean, literally, the
inside of my shoe
我的意思是，字面意思，就是我鞋子的内侧
has 4 ounces of peach tea in it.
里面有 4 盎司的桃茶。
I'm sorry, buddy.
It was an accident.
对不起，伙计。这是个意外。
But, how is it that you have
an accident every day, though?
但是，您为什么每天都会发生事故呢？
You have ruined 90
percent of my shoes.
你毁了我 90% 的鞋子。
-Yeah?
-90 percent.
-是的？-90%。
But nobody else's shoes!
Look around!
但没有其他人的鞋子！睤！
There's 60 people in here!
这里有 60 个人！
I'll take it.
-No one else's shoes have been affected!
我会接受的。- 没有其他人的鞋子受到影响！
I'll take it.
-This is a #### conspiracy.
我会接受的。- 这是一个 #### 阴谋。
I'll take it, because I
thought you were going to say
我接受它，因为我以为你会说
"I've ruined 90
percent of your life".
“我毁了你 90% 的生活”。
That's what I thought you were
going to say. I'll take the shoes.
我以为你会这么说。我来拿鞋子。